# **Curriculum Vitae**

# **Programmer**



#### **PROFILE**

Name: Noor Alizah Afifah R

Email: nooralizahar@gmail.com

Phone: 085884571705

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/noor-alizah-afifah-r-826630148/

Birth: Makassar - Sept 25, 2000

High: 158cm Weight: 50kg Religion: Islam

- Highly motivated programmers with 2 years of work experience, with more than 4
  years in the programming world. I have worked extensively on websites and mobile
  developers. Carry out different and challenging responsibilities.
- Successfully working on projects with good results and meeting client requests.
- experience in building good teamwork.

#### **COMPETENCIES**

PHP MYSQL DB

Python POSTGRES DB

VB.Net SQL SERVER

Bootstrap Framework JavaScript

Laravel Framework Django Framework

Codelgniter Framework IONIC Framework

Photoshop Hardware Service

Database Design System Design

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**KOIN (Toko Indonesia)** 

Indonesia

Project Mobile Apps Consumer and Inventory Sales System

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as a programmer that supports the creation of websites

and mobile apps for companies

PT.MAAI Indonesia

Project Hajj and Umrah Management System

Role Remote Web Developer

Objectives Acting as a Hajj and Umrah system developer that has been

running

Pratista Skin Care Indonesia

Project Company Profile and Consultation Website

Role Web Programmer

(February 2020 - April 2020)

Objectives Acting as the creator of a consultation website for skin care Pratista

#### Yayasan Al-Azhary Indonesia

Indonesia

Project Web Profile SMP Al-Azhary Cianjur

Role Web Programmer

(February 2020)

Objectives Acting as the creator of a web profile SMP Al-Azhary Cianjur

### Yayasan Al-Azhary Indonesia

Indonesia

Project Web Profile SMA Al-Azhary Cianjur

Role Web Programmer

(March 2020)

Objectives Acting as the creator of a web profile SMA Al-Azhary Cianjur

NFS Community 2020

Indonesia

Project NFS Community Website

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as the developer of the website NFS Community Website

### PT. Natieva Global Internasional

Indonesia

Project E-Archive System

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as the developer of the website E-Archive System for the Ministry

of PUPR

### PT. Natieva Global Internasional

Indonesia

Project Web Loan Management System

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as the developer of the website loan management system for

the Ministry of PUPR

### PT. Natieva Global Internasional

Indonesia

Project CRM System

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as the developer of the website CRM System for the Company

## Kementrian Perindustrian

PT. Indo Solusi Lestari

Project

Indonesia

Project Siva Website

Role Programmer

Objectives Acting as the developer of the website Siva for the Ministry of Industry

Indonesia

Role Web Programmer

(March 2020)

Web Company Profile

Objectives Acting as the creator of a web company profile PT. Indo Solusi Lestari

## **WORK HISTORY**

PT. Natieva Global Internasional	Indonesia
Remote Programmer	2020 – Present
PT. Toko Indonesia	Indonesia
Programmer	2019 – 2020
PT. MAAI	Indonesia
Web Developer	2020
Freelancer	Indonesia
Web Developer	2018 – Present

## **EDUCATION**

Gunadarma University	Indonesia
Bachelor of Computer Science	2018 – 2022
Magister of Computer Science	2022 - 2023